continue to see a significant runway for Kesimpta I think a lot of that
performance in the US is down to strong operational execution we've gotten much
better I think at targeting the right patient groups the right physician
groups as well as honing our messaging our
research around the unique benefits of Kesimpta as a self-administered monthly
therapy so excited about that we also continue to progress now our Q every two
months dose to Kesimpta which we're looking forward to reading out next year
now on in the ex-US setting 31 percent constant currency growth strong growth
in Europe we estimate one in six MS patients now are in Kesimpta we see 79
percent of patients that are coming on to Kesimpta either as naive or first
switch in the EU five we also have continued NBRX leadership at nine out of
ten major markets we do find in general outside of the US a strong interest in
self-administered medicines that can get patients out of the hospital or out
of needing ongoing visits for infusions so very amenable to the symptoms profile
and we see an opportunity for continued expansion with two-thirds of DMT treated
patients continuing to not be on a B cell therapy in our key market
now moving to slide eight PluVicto continued a strong rollout particularly driven by the
pre-taxing crmcrpc setting we saw strong demand and we also saw good progress on our ex-US rollout
starting with the US we saw the US sales growth 76 percent in in the quarter with 70 over 70
percent of that business now coming from the pre-taxing setting and that's coming from a
mix of urologists and community
oncologists right now we estimate about over 60 percent of our NBRXs are coming from the
community I think that demonstrates we've not successfully made RLT a medicine that can be
prescribed in the in the community settings for patients who prefer to access care in the
community outside of the US we saw 48 percent growth with NBRXs up 92 percent this was driven
by strong EU uptake but also I think a notable solid start in Japan
where we're seeing very strong interest in PluVicto so we excited about that and the initial stages
of a launch as well in China as a reminder we have manufacturing sites that are being built and
getting up to speed now in Japan and China which will allow us to serve the Asian market so diving